HANNAH FOLK

Los Angeles, CA | (510) 557-5843 | hfolk25@gmail.com

Summary of Qualifications

Have a strong background in public speaking and teamwork through student leadership positions at UC San Diego. Experience with analysis and problem solving developed through coursework. Proficient in programming and web development. Understanding of economic concepts through coursework. Highly motivated individual who works well with others, demonstrated in multiple jobs and theatre experiences.

- Java
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Node.is
- Express

- MySQL
- React.js
- LaTex
- Microsoft Word, Excel, Powerpoint
- Outlook
- Written and oral communication

Education

- Bachelor of Science: Joint Mathematics and Economics, Phi Beta Kappa
- Bachelor of Arts: Theatre

University of California, San Diego

Graduation: June 2019 Overall GPA: 3.78

Experience

• Tour Guide, Warner Bros. Studio Facilities

(June 2019 – Present)

- Conduct tours of Warner Bros. studio lot, highlighting the company's history while connecting to modern-day productions, resulting in guests' better understanding of a working entertainment studio
- College Ambassador, UC San Diego Office of Admissions

(Jan 2018 – Present)

- Provide campus tours to 70,000 prospective and admitted students and their family members
- Organize large-scale events with over 25,000 visitors to the university open-house day "Triton Day"
- Manage the front desk of a busy tours office, answering admissions questions and phone calls, addressing the concerns of UC San Diego visitors
- Stage Management Intern, The Old Globe

(July 2018 – Sept 2018)

- Assisted a stage management team at a prominent theatre, informing the head stage managers of any immediate issues to ensure the rehearsal room runs smoothly
- Wrote notes addressing actors' errors to fully capture the intent of both the director and playwright
- Orientation Leader, UCSD Sixth College

(Apr 2017 – Sept 2017)

 Welcomed incoming first-year and transfer students to UC San Diego, resulting in students' better understanding of the school and an increase in their preparation for the upcoming school years

Organizations

• UCSD Ski and Snowboard Team

(Nov. 2018 to June 2019)

Christians at UCSD

(Sept. 2015 to June 2019)

• UC San Diego Tennis Club

(Oct. 2015 to June 2018)